http://www.msspower.com.au/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Our policy regarding the personal information we collect about you.
1. Introduction
This policy covers MSS Power's use of personal information that MSS Power collects when you use the MSS Power website located at
http://www.msspower.com.au and subdomains. The policy also gives you information about use of
cookies; and how you may reject such cookies. From time to time, you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g.
name and email address) in order to receive or use services on our website. Such services include newsletters, competitions, pricing data,
returns authorisations, and purchases. By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable MSS Power and its service providers to
provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with
this policy. When using your personal information MSS Power will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet
best practice.
2. Visitor Information
During the course of any visit to the MSS Power website, the pages you see, along with a short text file called a 'cookie' are downloaded
to your computer. Many websites do this, because cookies enable website publishers to do useful things like find out whether the computer
(and probably its user) has visited the website before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left
there on the last visit.
Information supplied by cookies can help us to provide you with a better online user experience, such as storing your preferences. MSS Power
does not share cookie information with any other organisation.
MSS Power uses a service called "Google Analytics" to allow MSS Power to better track usage of the web site by customers and to analyse
from that track usage which campaigns and which websites and functions are popular and which are not. The Google Analytics service adopted
by MSS Power tracks visitors using cookies and does not divulge any personal information about the user/visitor to the website. It simply
uses the IP address to generate reports containing general numbers of visits, popular web pages etc.
Please note that if you do not wish Google Analytics to operate and generate reports in respect of your usage of the MSS Power website you
can block the use of cookies on your PC. In that instance data cannot be collected on your website usage by Google Analytics.This is
your right. Please note that there may be some loss of functionality if you do disable cookies. Please see below for further
information concerning cookies or visit
http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/ to learn about Google
Policies and Principles.
3. What is a cookie?
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's
computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow
it. To protect your privacy your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to
you by other sites.
Many websites do this whenever a user visits in order to track online traffic flows.
Cookies record information about your online preferences, and store such information relevant to your current visit such as a unique
session identifier. As stated above this is the purpose of Google Analytics - to track usage and trends of the MSS Power web site. Users
have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any
time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalised services cannot then be provided to that user and accordingly you may
not be able to take full advantage of all of the MSS Power website features. Each browser is different; so check the "Help" menu of your
browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.
For further information on cookies please visit http://www.aboutcookies.org.
4. Use and storage of your personal information
When you supply any personal information to the MSS Power website for online ordering, user account setup, etc. we have legal obligations
towards you in the way we use the data. We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it and tell you if
we want to pass the information on to anyone else (see the notices on particular webpages that let you know why we are requesting the
information). In general information that you provide to MSS Power will only be used within MSS Power (and by its agents and service
providers).
Your information will be disclosed where we are obliged or permitted by law. Also, if you post or send offensive, inappropriate or
objectionable content anywhere on or to the MSS Power website or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour, MSS Power can use whatever
information is available to it about you to stop such behaviour. This may involve informing relevant third parties such as your employer,
Internet provider and law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour.
We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event
that the purpose has been met, or so long as statutory records must be kept e.g. purchase data/payments etc. Where personal information is
held for entities that are not yet clients but have registered information with MSS Power, that information will be held as long as is
necessary to ensure that the service is run smoothly. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance
with relevant Data Protection laws. As explained above the implementation of Google Analytics by MSS Power does not involve the retention
of personal information.
5. Access to your personal information
You have the right to request a copy of the personal information MSS Power holds about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. We
charge AU$30 for information requests. Please direct requests to a MSS Power Customer Services Representative by emailing
sales@msspower.com.au
6. How to find and control your cookies, If you are using Netscape 6.0
On your taskbar click:
6. Check the 'override automatic cookie handing' box
7. Select Accept, Block or Prompt for action as appropriate.
If you are using Netscape Communicator 4.0
On your taskbar click:
If you are using Firefox 8.0
On your taskbar click:
1. Firefox
2. Preferences
3. Privacy
4. Set 'Firefox Will:' to 'Use customer settings for history'
If you are using Internet Explorer 9.0, 8.0 or 7.0
On your taskbar click:
If you are using Internet Explorer 6.0
On your taskbar click:
If you are using Internet Explorer 5.0 or 5.5
On your taskbar click:
1. Tools
2. Internet Options
3. Security Tab
4. Custom Level
5. Scroll down to the sixth option to see how cookies are handled by IE5 and select Accept or Disable, or Prompt for action as appropriate.
If you are using Internet Explorer 3.0
On your taskbar click:
1. Options
2. Advanced
3. 'Warn before Accepting Cookies' button
7. How do you know which of the sites you have visited use cookies, if you are using Netscape 6.0?
On your taskbar click:
If you are using Netscape Communicator 4.0
Netscape bundles all cookies into one file on your hard drive. On Windows machines you will need to find the file called Cookie.txt.
If you are using Internet Explorer 9.0, 8.0 or 7.0
On your taskbar click:
1. Tools
2. Safety
3. Web Page Privacy Policy
If you are using Internet Explorer 5.0 or 6.0
On your taskbar click:
If you are using Internet Explorer 4.0
On your taskbar click:
1. View
2. Internet Options
3. General tab (the default tab)
4. Settings
5. View Files
If you are using Internet Explorer 3.0
On your taskbar click:
8. How to see your cookie code
Just click on a cookie to open it. You will see a short string of text and numbers. The numbers are your identification card, which can
only be seen by the server that gave you the cookie.
9. List of msspower.com.au cookies
Cookies and what they are used for:
Cookie name
va
Purpose
This cookie is only used in a logged in module of the website. A unique identifier given each time the site is accessed (via logging in).
The cookie is used to assist the backend application retain the login id and account information, so that a login is not required on every
page accessed.
Persistence
Expires 1 hour from last loaded/logged in page
We regularly monitor this website and will update this list of cookies when necessary.
Click here for a list of
Google Analytics cookies
Sign In
Enter your Legend Pass and password below.
Forgot password?
Setup Email Account
If you have an old login, please enter the account number in the LEGEND PASS field and the old password in the password field below and you will be directed to the LEGEND PASS Authorisation Page to complete your personalised login.
Never signed in before?
Learn more about LEGEND PASS.
Forgot Password
Enter your Legend Pass or old account number below.
< Back to login
If you have entered an old account number the password reset email will go to the web account owner.
If you have entered a LEGEND PASS then the password reset email will be sent to the email address linked to your LEGEND PASS.
Setup Email Account
Enter your email address below.
< Back to login
Please enter your email address and business postcode. An email will be sent to you with further instructions.
